{
  "201": {
    "quiz-1":[
      {
        "question":"Which is a correct example of concatenation in JavaScript?",
        "possibleAnswers": ["'I brush my ' + bodyPart + ' in the morning'", "'hello' + 'there' userName", "I like to eat + bananas", "'dogs run through the parking lot all happy' + and stuff"],
        "correctAnswers":["possibleAnswers[0]"]
      },
      {
        "question":"What tag do you need to run JavaScript code in an html file?",
        "possibleAnswers":["<p></p>", "<script></script>","<js></js>","<javascript></javascript>"],
        "correctAnswers":["possibleAnswers[1]"]
      },
      {
        "question":"Which is not a data type?",
        "possibleAnswers":["attribute","string","array","boolean"],
        "correctAnswers":["possibleAnswers[0]"]
      },
      {
        "question":"What command would we use to create and switch to a new branch called debug in Git?",
        "possibleAnswers":["git branch new debug","git checkout -b debug","git branch debug","git checkout debug"],
        "correctAnswers":["possibleAnswers[1]"]
      },
      {
        "question":"Which defines the structure of a webpage?",
        "possibleAnswers":["JS","CSS","GitHub","HTML"],
        "correctAnswers":["possibleAnswers[3]"]
      },
      {
        "question":"When writing clean code, which should you avoid?",
        "possibleAnswers":["syntax highlighting","step by step instructions","no whitespace","fixed-width font"],
        "correctAnswers":["possibleAnswers[2]"]
      },
      {
        "question":"What Unix command would create a new directory called thursday?",
        "possibleAnswers":["mkdir thursday","directory thursday","new directory thursday","newdir thursday"],
        "correctAnswers":["possibleAnswers[0]"]
      },
      {
        "question":"Which of these combinations evaluates to true?",
        "possibleAnswers":["true && true","true && false","false && true","false && false","true || true","true || false","false || true","false || false"],
        "correctAnswers":["possibleAnswers[0]","possibleAnswers[4]", "possibleAnswers[5]", "possibleAnswers[6]"]
      },
      {
        "question":"Analyze this block of code.",
        "codeSnippet":["1: var gopher = 1;","2: if (gopher < 10)","3:    console.log(gopher);","4: } else {","5:   console.log('potato');","6: }"],
        "possibleAnswers":["Yes","No - Line 2","No - Line 1","No - Line 3"],
        "correctAnswers":["possibleAnswers[1]"]
      },
      {
        "question":"Which is not an example of a JavaScript statement?",
        "possibleAnswers":["6 *= 5;","var NumBooks;","1 =! loneliestNumber;","userName = userName.toUpperCase();"],
        "correctAnswers":["possibleAnswers[2]"]
      }
    ]
  },
  "301": {
    "quiz-1":[]
  }
}
